德古拉  前情提要
Previously on "Dracula"...
你的人  Hackett  他袭击了Mina
Your man, Hackett, he attacked Mina.
谁让你来的？ Grayson吗？
Who sent you here? It was Grayson, wasn't it?
我应属于你  你亦应属于我
I belong to you, and you belong to me.
我爱你  Mina
I love you, Mina.
你得走了
You need to leave.
是得让她尝尝那种痛了
Someone should teach her such pain.
Jonathan
Jonathan.
恶龙会烧死了我的妻儿
The Order burned my wife and children.
我会复仇的
I will have my revenge.
孩子们！
The children!
欢迎来到龙之会  Harker先生
Welcome, Mr. Harker, to the Order of the Dragon.
Grayson的科研以死告终
Grayson's technology is a dead end.
- 我们需要帮助  - 你需要我扮演犹大
- We need your help. - You'd have me play Judas.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen, this
这台机器会威胁公众安全  关闭它
machine is a threat to public safety. Shut it down.
在伦敦还有更年老的吸血鬼
There is another elder vampire in London.
更多吸血鬼聚现伦敦  响应他的召唤
He's infested London with creatures, answering his call.
- 谁召唤的你？  - Dracula
- Who called you? - Dracula.
如果他们想要战争  那么我们给他战争
If it's a war they want, then it's a war they're gonna get.
这些傲慢的混蛋早该没命了
These arrogant bastards have sealed their own fate.
现在该他们看着我大获胜利
Now, they'll see the violence I can reap.
先生  您对抗恶龙会不是一两天了
Sir, you insist the Order was behind the attack
早在Murray小姐被袭击前两周
on Miss Murray, when not a fortnight ago, you concluded
我被那些流氓贼寇绑去
that my abduction was the
您就应得出此结论
work of a rogue element within their ranks.
- 这不同  - 没什么不同  那女人…
- This is different. - No, this is the same. The woman...
Janina Kleiberson  她为恶龙会效力
Janina Kleiberson, a known contractor to the Order.
反复的询问谁是你最爱的人
Repeatedly asked me what it was you loved.
然后那三联画…您妻子的画像
Then, the triptych... A painting of your wife, yes,
极像Murray小姐的画像被偷
but the very image of Mina Murray was stolen
然后被Davenport大人回收
and then recovered from Lord Davenport's study.
回收？什么时候？
Recovered? When?
今晚  我的线人
Tonight. Some agents of
在这特殊的夜晚提供这一消息
mine will be delivering it this very evening,
您能让我说完吗？
and will you please let me finish?
- 我以为你说完了  - 是Davenport干的
- I thought you had. - It was Davenport,
他命人袭击我  不是恶龙会
not the Order, who ordered my attack,
还偷了三联画
stole the triptych,
也是他的人袭击了Murray小姐
and it was his men who attacked miss Murray.
所以呢？
Your point?
这是针对您的个人仇杀
This was a personal vendetta against you,
完全无关他在恶龙会的地位
completely unrelated to his position in the Order of the Dragon.
不  这就是高层的恶棍
No. This stinks of High Council.
他们懦弱无能的
Their cowardly tactic of
袭击敌人的妻子和孩子们
attacking the wives and children of their enemies.
- 先生  我知道…  - 他们用酸…
- Sir, I know... - To attack her with acid...
抹杀她的美貌  造成毁容
To obliterate her beauty, to disfigure her...
这不是一个男人
This is not the act of one
为儿子复仇应有的行为
man seeking vengeance for his son's death,
但破坏者的招数我一清二楚
but a pack of vandals I know all too well.
潜行和玩诡计的时光已然不再
The time for stealth and scheming has passed.
从今夜起  直至他们屈服  都会
From this night and every night until they yield...
血流成河
Blood will flow.
你去哪了？我一直在找你
Where have you been? I've been looking for you.
你需要马上去Carfax Manor庄园
You're needed at Carfax Manor immediately.
我不认为你很了解情况  教授
I don't think you quite understand the situation, Professor.
相反地  Renfield先生
On the contrary, Mr. Renfield.
正是你不了解
It is you who does not understand.
简单说  你的老板和我有一个合同
Put quite simply, your client and I had a contract.
我提供专业技术
I would provide technical skills,
他负责促进其发展
he would promote that technology.
你和他一起  会毁掉你们共同的敌人
And together, you and he would destroy your common enemy.
本是如此  在这其中
Would have, had your client
他应克制他的人类情感
restrained his passion to be human,
但是他没有
but he did not,
而随后  他又失去了磁共振器
and in the process, he lost possession of the resonator.
现在  我们计划失败  合同无效了
And now, our plan has failed, and the contract is broken.
现在  请你…
Now, please, if you will excuse me...
他打算对恶龙会采取直接行动
He intends to take direct action against the Order.
教授  他很不在状态
Professor, he's quite beside himself.
- 你真需要和他谈谈  - Renfield先生
- You really must speak with him. - Mr. Renfield.
你的老板要如何做我已不再关心
What your client chooses to do is no longer my concern.
他们会陆续到达
They're arriving. Every huntsman
欧洲每一个值得关注的猎人
of note from every chapter house in Europe.
我们将清扫整个伦敦
Oh, we're going to sweep across London,
深挖每一个角落
root out every one of the swine,
剿灭每一只毒害
and butcher them in their lairs.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
我孩子们绑架了
My children have been abducted.
都出去  快
Clear the room. Now.
来吧
Come along.
一切都与此相关
It's linked to all of this.
我们的人发现了这个
Our men recovered that
在给Davenport房子消毒的时候
while they were sanitizing Davenport's house.
他的儿子Daniel写的
His son, Daniel, wrote it.
显然是封遗书
It's clearly a suicide note.
Daniel和Laurent大人是恋人？
Daniel and Lord Laurent were lovers?
Alexander Grayson不仅仅是个狡猾的商人
Alexander Grayson is not only a cunning businessman,
他还策划犯罪  徇私舞弊
he is a criminal mastermind, prepared to cheat,
勒索敲诈  杀害所有挡道之人
blackmail, or murder anyone who stands in his way.
但为什么？  他为什么绑架你孩子？
But why? Now, why would he abduct your children?
这对他的目的有何作用？
How could that possibly further his ends?
他的目的可不是表里如一
His ends are not what they seem.
能源计划
This energy scheme of his
仅仅是到达目的的一种手段
is merely a means to a very different end,
他的目的是破坏组织
and that is the destruction of this organization.
从他到伦敦起  我们不断受到袭击…
Since he arrived in London, we have been under attack...
个别委员  我们的金融安全
Individual members, our financial security,
而现在  是我的孩子
and now, my children.
但Grayson的动机是什么？
But what motive does Grayson have?
Grayson没有动机  但Dracula有
Grayson has none, but Dracula,
现在境况完全不同
that is a different matter entirely.
此次侵扰只是分散我们的注意力
This infestation is merely a distraction,
是为了不让我们怀疑Grayson
a feinting maneuver that allows him to strike us
而做的幌子
at will in the guise of Alexander Grayson.
很显然你仍坚信Grayson是个吸血鬼
Surely you can't still believe that Grayson is a vampire.
你也亲眼目睹他处于光天化日之下
You've seen him in broad daylight with your own eyes.
也许他是找到一些方法保护自己…
Perhaps he's found some way to protect himself...
一些巫术类的
Some sorcery.
看看你自己
Listen to yourself.
精神错乱了吧
This is insanity.
重要的是  你不能这样
Or more importantly, it is off the point.
我们面对的是圣经中描述的威胁
We face a threat of biblical proportions.
这我知道  但是Grayson
I'm aware of that, but Grayson...
在适当的时候会处理Grayson的
Grayson will be dealt with in due course,
但现在  你必须把全部精力放在这场危机上
but for now, I must demand your full attention on this crisis.
- 但我的孩子 - 难道要我发誓吗？
- But my children... - Must I quote the Primary Oath?
Jonathan
Jonathan.
Harker先生?
Mr. Harker...?
Lucy?
你干了什么?
What have you done?
监制  翻译：幸福ing形式
翻译：格  依依
翻译  校对：小鱼  老马
校对  后期：幸福ing形式
祝各位观影愉快
德古拉  第一季第九集
—— 真爱字幕组  出品 ——
仔细搜查整幢建筑
Search the carriage house
里里外外都不能放过
and any outbuildings or sheds.
Lassiter 去检查佣人房间
Lassiter, check the servants' quarters,
再派两个人上去检查阁楼
and send two men up to check on the attic!
- 遵命 先生 - 这里您管事?
- Right you are, sir. - Are you charge here?
是的  那么你是?
Yes, I am, and who may you be?
R.M.Renfield 我是Grayson先生的代理人
R. M. Renfield, esquire. I'm Mr. Grayson's attorney.
您一定是有搜查令的
I presume you have a warrant.
由法官签署
Signed by a magistrate.
一切都是合法的
Everything's in order.
很难说
Hardly.
这里没有提到你们在找什么
There's no mention of what it is you're searching for.
没有说明  就是无效的
Without it, this is invalid.
我请您和您的人
I demand you remove yourself
尽快离开这里
and your men from these premises immediately.
不然呢？
Or what?
不然我将不得不指控您的非法侵入
Or I shall be forced to press charges of criminal trespassing.
抱歉
Sorry.
还有蓄意破坏
And vandalism.
也许我也应该以妨碍调查的罪名拘捕你
Perhaps I should arrest you for obstructing an investigation.
究竟是什么调查?
An investigation into what, exactly?
他们在找我的孩子们  Renfield先生
They're looking for my children, Mr. Renfield.
尽管如此  先生
Be that as it may, sir,
在他们把合法的搜查令
they shall have to desist
带来以前  他们必须停止搜查
until they return with a properly executed warrant.
一派胡言
Nonsense.
我已经通知了Salinger督查
I've already informed inspector Salinger
他的人可以随意搜查这里
that his men are free to search this property,
只要能对他们的调查有帮助
if only to speed their investigation.
你在这里不会找到任何孩子  Browning先生
You'll find no children at Carfax, Mr. Browning.
虽然我经常渴望听到他们的笑声
Although I've often longed for their laughter...
还有小脚啪嗒啪嗒走的声音
And the pitter-patter of tiny feet.
抱歉占用了你的宝贵时间
I'm sorry to have wasted your time,
但是我是有原因的
but I have my reasons.
没事  没什么好道歉的  先生
No, no, nothing to apologize for, sir.
就我的猜测  这只是个开始
As far as I'm concerned, this is just a start.
有半数的委员会成员听我的指挥
Commissioner's got half the met under my command on this.
我们会找到你的孩子的
We will find your children.
谢谢您  督查  我可怜的妻子已经快崩溃了
Thank you, Inspector. My poor wife is beside herself.
是啊  一定是的  你最好是多照顾照顾她
Yes. Yes, I'm sure she is. Best you look after her.
如果有什么消息我会联系你的
I'll contact you personally if anything comes up.
- 不论好坏 - 是的 先生
- Be it good or bad. - Yes, sir.
- Harker - 别出声 快上来
- Harker. - Shush. Get in, quickly.
这就是可耻的人做的事
This is what happens when you're vile.
他以为敌人会用和他一样的手段
You assume your enemies would sink to similar tactics.
令人作呕
Disgusting.
你不会认为是Van Helsing?
- You don't suppose Van Helsing...
绑架了Browning的孩子们?
Abducted Browning's children?
毋庸置疑
Doubtful.
这个男人会严格执行自己的计划
The man's a martinet, enslaved to his own scheme.
为了确保他的目标会实现
He'd rather self-immolate
就算是牺牲自己也在所不惜
than stray from that rut he calls a path.
这点我真不确定 先生
I wouldn't be so sure about that, sir.
他自己说过他在考虑和您的伙伴关系
He said himself he considered your partnership over.
他说过?
Did he?
什么时候
And when did he tell you this?
我认为明智的做法是告诉他你的计划
I thought it prudent to inform him of your plan
让他直接参与进来  先生
to directly engage the Order, sir.
是么?
Really?
你觉得这很明智  Renfield?
Did you think it prudent, Renfield?
难道现在你来指挥我了么?
Am I now your charge, and you my caretaker?
没有  先生
No, sir, I o...
你是对的  先生  我过界了
You're quite right, sir. I overstepped my bounds.
我和你保证  不会再发生了
I assure you, it will not happen again.
刚刚是Alastair
That was Alastair.
我告诉他你有点不舒服
I told him you've been feeling unwell.
他很担心你
He's worried about you.
拜托 Lucy
Please, Lucy.
告诉我到底发生了什么
You must tell me what's going on.
我知道我不像
I know I'm not as
Jayne Wetherby那么精明时髦  但是
sophisticated or modern as Jayne Wetherby, but...
我也不是个傻子
I'm not a complete fool.
亲爱的
Darling...
告诉我吧
Please tell me.
- 你为什么不告诉我? - 告诉你什么
- Why didn't you tell me? - Tell you what?
一个女人爱上
That it's perfectly natural
另一个女人是那么自然的事
for a woman to fall in love with another woman.
谁?
To what?
我和Mina
For me and Mina to...
你在说什么?
What are you saying?
天哪 上帝
Oh, my God.
够了 在这里停下
That's far enough. Pull over here.
哦! 哦
Whoa! Whoa.
我决定接受你的建议
I've decided to accept your offer...
就待您回答一个问题
Pending your answer to one question.
什么问题
And that is?
为什么要指使人袭击Mina Murray？
Why did the Order attack Mina Murray?
袭击? 你未婚妻? 真是荒谬
Attack? Your fiance? That's ridiculous.
我们想招募你  不是和你树敌
We're trying to recruit you, not make an enemy of you.
Davenport是幕后黑手
Davenport was behind it.
如果是他  那我向你保证
If he was, then I assure you,
这是未经批准的
it was unsanctioned.
据我们所知  他已经...
Had we known about it, he would've been...
你杀了他
You killed him.
你真是充满惊喜啊  Harker先生
You are full of surprises, Mr. Harker.
- 我会被处罚么? - 被我们? 上帝 不会
- Will I punished? - By us? Good God, no.
在我们的队伍里
Rogue actions are not tolerated
恶行是不被允许的
within the ranks,
特别是在他们悖逆了我们的目标时
especially when they run counter to our objectives.
何况  我从来没有关心过Davenport
Besides, I never did much care for Davenport.
我觉得你已经得到了满意的答案
I trust I've answered your question to your satisfaction.
是的
You have.
那么 欢迎你  Harker先生
Then, welcome, Mr. Harker...
欢迎加入龙之会
To the Order of the Dragon.
我们要你做的第一件事  Harker先生
The first thing we need you to do, Mr. Harker,
把Grayson的共鸣器蓝图拿来
is bring us the blueprints of Grayson's resonator.
共鸣器电路图
Resonator Schematics
Harker先生  原来您还在
Mr. Harker, I didn't know you were still here.
我拿些信件
I was just catching up on some correspondence.
Alexander今晚有什么安排吗？
Will Alexander be needing anything else tonight?
不清楚
I doubt it.
他没告知就离开了
He just left,
我想他会很晚回来
and I suspect he will be quite late.
好 那我也走了
Well, then, I suppose I'll be off as well.
Harker先生？
Mr. Harker?
嗯
Yes?
如果可以
If you could, please convey
请代我和Grayson先生
my and Mr. Grayson's warmest regards
向Murray女士问好
to Miss Murray.
好的
I'll do that.
你在这儿干嘛？
What are you doing here?
Renfield说你似乎认为
Renfield tells me that you're under the impression
我们的合作要终止了
that our partnership has come to an end.
恐怕如此
I see no alternative.
你的不自控
Your inability to control
完全毁坏了我们的计划
yourself has completely derailed our scheme.
如果我重获共鸣器就不会了
Not if I regain possession of the resonator.
一个示威
One demonstration,
组织便会破产  如计划的一样
and the Order Draco will be rendered bankrupt, as planned.
没错  Renfield告知了
Yes, Renfield told me.
另一场屠杀
Another bloodbath.
称之为策略也掩藏不了冲动的本性
Calling it a strategy does not make it any less a compulsion.
教授  你不会不知道
Professor, you wouldn't happen to know anything
Browning的两个孩子消失的事吧
about the disappearance of Browning's two children?
- 与你何干？ - 没什么
- What is it to you? - Nothing.
只是因此
Only that it places undue
当局对我们的监视力度加大了
scrutiny on our activities by the authorities,
如果我们的计划失败
and if our plan should fail as a result,
我会让你负全责
I'll hold you solely responsible.
那样的话 Abraham
And then, Abraham...
会有你好果子吃
You're going to have a very, very bad day.
我先离开了  和朋友用餐
Now, if you'll excuse me. I'm dining with friends tonight.
爸爸 爸爸 爸爸
Papa! Papa! Papa!
爸爸 爸爸
Papa! Papa!
- 好球 - 好球
- Cheers. - Cheers.
台球啊
Ah, billiards.
Grayson 我不知道你是会员啊
Grayson, I had no idea you were a member.
Rothcroft 对吧？
Rothcroft, isn't it?
我真希望你再中断比赛
I do hope you'll pardon the interruption.
大陆的朋友
Relatives of mine from the continent.
我邀请他们来伦敦
I invited them to London
承诺这里的佳肴
with the promise that the cuisine here is...
美味极了
Excellent.
你不是美国人吗？
Aren't you American?
孩子们  好好享用
Bon appetite, boys.
休息吧
Sleep.
这些是你送的
They're from you.
是
Yes.
我以为…
I thought...
- 我以为是Jonathan - 不
- I thought Jonathan... - No.
- 你在现场 - 哪儿？
- You were there. - Where?
- 你阻止了那些人 - 别再想那些了
- You stopped those men. - Don't think about it, ever.
那些人不会再接近你
None of those men will ever touch you again.
我知道
I know.
你想的事子虚乌有
Whatever you think happened didn't happen.
我不在场
I wasn't there.
我在Carfax庄园
I was at Carfax.
不
No.
不 你在
No, you were there.
我要走了
I have to go.
别 能 再呆会儿吗？
Please... please, will you stay a little longer?
不行
I can't.
你不知道我多想这样  但…
You don't know how much I want to, but...
不行
I can't.
为什么
Why?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我想这是他们的宣战
I believe they call this a declaration of war.
真不可思议
It's astonishing.
竟然没想隐藏尸体
No effort to conceal the bodies whatsoever.
动机也是  大胆 无耻 而华丽
Nor the cause. It's bold, brazen, flamboyant.
我从未见过这样的情况
I've never seen its like.
- 这些人呢 - Yard有名的合作人
- And these men? - Known associates from the Yard.
今晚报刊会报道这五位绅士
This evening's edition will report how these five gentlemen
在游艇不幸遇难
were part of a tragic yachting mishap...
沉入海底
Lost at sea.
只有“凶猛者”
Only the Fell One would
才会精心策划这样一场屠杀
dare to orchestrate a slaughter like this.
- Browning先生 - 检查员？
- Mr. Browning. - Inspector?
是的 先生
Yes, sir.
似乎浪费您的时间了
It seems I've wasted your time.
我刚从我妻子的妹妹那里收到消息
I've just had word from my
我的孩子和她在一起
wife's sister that my children are with her.
错误的电报消息  严重的混淆
An errant telegram, a terrible mix-up.
- 那他们安全？ - 安然无恙
- They're safe then? - Safe and sound.
真是太不好意思了
I can't tell you how embarrassed I am.
不不 我懂了 先生
No, no. Say no more, sir.
- 安全就好 - 是的
- Better to be safe than sorry. - Yes.
如果您不介意
Now, if you don't mind,
我要单独和我同事聊聊
I'd like a quiet word with my colleagues.
当然 先生 伙计们
Of course, sir. All right, men.
Browning先生  这是Kaha Ruma
Mr. Browning, this is Kaha Ruma.
毛利战士的后代
He's descended from Maori warriors,
我们的猎人领导之一
one of our leading huntsmen.
- 先生 久仰大名 - 深感荣幸
- Your reputation precedes you, sir. - Pleasure.
- 我召唤了西西里人 - Loiza Scaverra？
- I've summoned the Sicilian. - Loiza Scaverra?
你们会需要先知者 他很在行
You'll need a good seer. He's the best.
罗马教廷的红衣主教Valachi
Cardinal Valachi from the Vatican chapter's
也同意将Sanguinem Sanctorum借给我们
also agreed to lend us the Sanguinem Sanctorum.
神圣遗物
A most sacred relic.
Browning先生 您的孩子呢
Mr. Browning, your children, sir?
行踪未知
Still missing,
但不能让笨警察瞎搅和
but we can't have the police bungling about,
上帝保佑报社能获得消息
and God help us if the press get a hold of it.
你质疑我对Grayson的判断是对的
You were right to question my judgment about Grayson.
我情绪激动了
I was distraught.
但他对我们依旧是个威胁
That said, he's still a threat to us.
当然  先生
It's no doubt, sir.
这样  你负责这个
Therefore, while you deal
“传染”病  我负责他
with this infestation, I shall deal with him.
同时  如果需要什么帮助的话
In the meantime, if there's anything you need,
任何帮助  我都可以提供
anything at all, I am at your service.
整体来说  这肯定包括
Above all, this must be contained,
无论是谁花的钱
no matter what the personal cost to any of us.
Lucy…
Lucy...
哦  不是吧
Oh, God.
他们对你做了什么？
What have they done to you?
- 他们怎么能这么做？  - 我不知道
- How could they? - I don't know.
我也一直很迷惑
I'm still so confused.
哦  Mina
Oh, Mina.
- Lucy  - 嗯？
- Lucy. - Yes?
- 你坐着我手了  - 哦  天啊  对不起
- You're sitting on my hand. - Oh, God, sorry.
我真笨
I'm such an oaf.
真漂亮
They're beautiful.
我采了十分之一个花园
I positively decimated the garden.
妈妈要发脾气了
Mother will have a fit.
Mina  我很抱歉
Mina, I'm so sorry.
只是你太出色  仁慈而已
It's just you're so smart and kind.
我简直不能想象有谁想要伤害你
I can't imagine anybody would ever want to hurt you.
这个世界上真的有人能伤害我的心  并且…
Breaks my heart that there are people in the world who would...
他会怎么样？
Who would what?
故意的…
Deliberately...
他们很漂亮
They're beautiful.
Jonathan？
Jonathan?
不不  我…我好久没见过他了  直到…
No, no. I-I haven't seen him since...
他出什么事了吗？
Has something happened to him?
没有
No.
不是  我的意思是  我不太清楚
No, I mean, not that I know of.
Lucy  告诉我事实
Lucy, tell me the truth.
你必须忘记Jonathan
You must forget about Jonathan.
- 什么？  - 不要问我了
- What? - Please don't ask me any questions.
你只要知道
You just have to know
他不是你认识的那个人就可以了
he's not the man you think he is.
你必须取消婚约
You must call off the engagement.
但是…那太疯狂了
But that's... that's insane.
我  我不能…我不能那么做
I-I can't... I can't do that.
- 你必须那么做  - 为什么？
- You must. - Why?
他做了什么？
What has he done?
他…
He...
- 我不能说  - Lucy…
- I can't. - Lucy...
别这么荒唐  告诉我
Don't be ridiculous. Just tell me.
你会讨厌我的
You're going to hate me.
我太对不起你了  Mina
I'm so sorry, Mina.
- 我太…  - 别
- I'm so... - Don't.
- 不…  - 出去！
- No... - Get out!
你滚  滚出去！
Get out, get out!
陷入绝地  永世不得升天
Romanian - "Within a closed circle, a place without escape"
Jonathan Harker…
Jonathan Harker...
你准备好
Are you prepared to take the Primary Oath
在我们兄弟和上帝面前
of the Order of the Dragon
接受组织的誓言了吗？
before your brethren and before your God?
准备好了
I am.
以我的生命
I swear on my life and the
还有那些我爱的人起誓  从今天起
lives of all those I love from this day forward,
我将把个人需求
I will never place my own needs
放在这神圣的使命后面
above those of this sacred Order,
所以  帮帮我吧上帝
so help me God.
给我五万英镑  否则孩子没命
我们一晚上屠戮了半个伦敦委员会的人
We slaughtered over half the London Council in a single night.
15年内将有更多的懦弱阴谋倒下
More blood drawn than in 15 years of cowardly scheming.
确实  但是这只是一小部分而已
It is but one chapter.
还有更多的等着我们呢
There are hundreds more.
也许吧  是的
Perhaps, yes,
但是我需要他们陷入极度恐慌
but I have this one in utter panic.
如果我白天攻击的话
Could you imagine their
你能想象他们的恐惧么
terror if I decided to attack in broad daylight?
先生  那绝对是不明智的
Sir, that would be inadvisable.
我们为数不多优于敌人的地方
One of the few advantages we still have over the enemy
就是他们没想到
is that they do not suspect
Dracula和Alexander Grayson是同一个人
Dracula and Alexander Grayson are one in the same.
如果你白天进攻的话
And if you were to attack by day,
我们就失去这个优势了
we would lose that advantage.
你去哪了？
Where have you been?
准备离开这个国家  我们一起
Preparing to leave the country, as should we all.
这就对了
That's right.
跑啊  小兔兔  跑吧
Run, little rabbit, run.
我敢肯定你老婆和你孩子会感到自豪的
I'm sure your wife and children would be very proud.
Alexander！Alexander我有好消息了
Alexander! Alexander, I have great news.
卫生局的判决对我们很有利
The board of Health ruled in our favor.
他们转移了隔离
They've removed the quarantine.
- 不可思议啊  - 是么  Abraham？
- Unbelievable. - Is it, Abraham?
长时间的舒适生活已经
Is it really so surprising that
让我们的敌人丧失了斗志  这很奇怪吗？
decades of soft living have neutered our enemies?
很明了的是
It's clear; they no longer
他们没有足够的时间来跟我们对峙了
have the stomach for direct confrontation.
所有的事情都没问题吧？
Is everything in order?
确实没什么问题
Indeed it appears so.
那么我们是不是开始我们的新游行了呢
And so we shall have our grand demonstration.
我希望你出席  Araham  如果不行的话
I hope you'll attend, Abraham, if not to assist,
至少见证下我们第一次决定性的胜利于…
at least to witness our first decisive victory over the...
竞争中
Competition.
好吧
Yes.
当然
Of course.
他为什么这么消沉？
Why is he so glum?
要知道  Kowalski先生
You know, Mr. Kowalski,
世界上有一些人
there are some men in this world
宁愿失去他们所有的一切
that would rather lose everything they have
也不愿意被证明是错的
than be proven wrong.
干的不错
Good job.
我刚刚收到卫生局的消息
I've just received word that the Board of Health...
允许游行人群继续前进？
Has allowed the demonstration to move forward?
是的  当然
Yes, of course.
Grayson先生怎么出意外了
How fortuitous for Mr. Grayson.
- 你安排的  - 不是我  Harker先生  是上帝
- You arranged it. - Not me, Mr. Harker. God.
我们都只是他的仆人
We are all merely His servants.
毕竟  如果没有这个游行的话
Besides, if there is no demonstration,
也许就不会失败了
there can be no failure.
先生你应该知道的
Sir, you should know,
Alexander Grayson是只比特斗牛犬
Alexander Grayson is a pit bull.
如果他失败了
If he fails, he'll simply
他会重头再来直到成功为止
regroup and keep trying until he succeeds.
我记住了
Noted.
谢谢你  Harker先生
Thank you, Mr. Harker.
天哪 这太棒了
Dear Lord, this is quite remarkable.
一切都很好 但是我们的目标是
That's all well and good, but our objective
确保没人敢再尝试一遍
is to make certain no one ever attempts this again.
我们必须制造一个完美的灾难
We must engineer a debacle so thorough
以至于没人会考虑把地磁
that no one will ever consider
作为一个可行资源
geomagnetism as a viable source of energy.
任何一台机器
Well, like any machine,
都有很多方法可以让它出故障
there are a number of ways to cause it to fail.
先生  我对故障没兴趣
I am not interested in failure, sir!
我想要一场灾难
I want a catastrophe!
医生
Doctor!
你在这儿干嘛
What are you doing here?
你怎么进来的？
How did you get in?
你给过我钥匙  不记得了？
You gave me a key, or don't you remember?
你去哪儿了？
Where have you been?
我
I...
你这两天去哪儿了
For the last two days, where have you been?
我 听着 我 我一直打算
I... look, I've... I've, um... I've been meaning to...
打算干嘛？
Meaning to what?
顺便来看看  来医院看我
Stop by? Visit me in hospital?
我想等到你更好一点的时候
I wanted to wait until you were stronger.
不管怎样
By all means.
是因为我太微不足道了吧
Because I'm such a delicate little thing.
- 你太贴心了 - 这不是我想说的
- How very thoughtful of you. - That's not what I'm saying.
为什么  Jonathan？
Why, Jonathan?
Lucy？
Lucy?
什么 她都告诉你什么了？
What... what did she tell you?
我需要知道的一切
Everything that I needed to know.
我不认为她会提到
Well, I don't suppose she mentioned
她过去两周都在我那儿呆着
that she's been throwing herself at me for the past two weeks.
你个猪头
You pig.
别碰我！
Don't touch me!
对不起
I'm sorry.
呃  你呃…呃…
Um, just... just...
你走吧…走吧
Just... just go. Just go.
你再也不会见到我了
You won't hear from me again.
为什么
Why?
- Jonathan  为什么  - 你知道为什么
- Jonathan, why? - You know why.
不
No...
我不知道
I don't.
因为你爱Grayson
Because you love Grayson.
哦！  注意点
Oy! Mind where you're going.
看着点路
Watch where you're going.
天哪  哦  天哪
Dear, oh, dear.
别挡路
Out of my way.
噢 噢 噢 吁
Whoa! Whoa, whoa, steady!
你
You.
是  就是我
Yes, me.
你回来了
You keep coming back.
我情不自禁
I can't help myself.
我又给你带来了一支
I brought you another.
真漂亮  谢谢
It's beautiful. Thank you.
发生什么了
What happened?
呃  我迷路了
Uh, I got lost.
医生说你可能得了脑震荡
The doctor says you may have a concussion.
是呀
Yes.
- 你是不是在外面溜达呢  - 没有呀
- Did you wander outside? - No, I didn't.
我出来了
I left.
我讨厌医院
I hate hospitals.
如果你要当医生
You know, that's gonna be a problem
这就是个大问题
when you become a doctor.
别逗我笑  这很痛的
Don't make me laugh. That hurts.
- 对不起  - 嗯
- I apologize. - Oh.
Alexander？
Alexander?
嗯哼？
Mm-hmm?
- 我们之间怎么了  - 我不知道
- What's happening between us? - I don't know.
我只能说…
All I can say is...
说吧
Please.
请继续
Please go on.
你让我想起了旧爱
You remind me of somebody I used to love.
她叫Ilona
Her name was Ilona.
我知道她
I know her.
从我还是个小女孩的时候
I have dreamed about her
我就开始关注她了
since I was a little girl.
我们俩很像
She looks like me.
我今晚看到她了
I saw her tonight.
我从水坑的反射中看到她了
I saw her in a reflection in a puddle,
她向我伸出手 就像她想要…
and she reached out to me, as if she was going to...
我在这儿
I'm here.
我就在这儿
I'm right here.
你爱我吗
Do you love me?
- 别这么问我  - 说吧
- Don't ask me that. - Tell me.
我不能
I can't.
我必须要完成一件事
I have something that I have to finish,
只要我做了  就不能前进
and until I do, I cannot move forward.
共振器
The resonator.
是的  但是这只是最小的一部分
Yes, but that's only the smallest part.
我欠旧爱的债
I owe that someone that I used to love a terrible debt,
直到全部付清之前…
and until it's paid in full...
我不能
I can't.
而且…
Besides...
你爱Harker
You love Harker.
不  都结束了
No, that's finished.
永远结束了
Never again.
为什么
Why?
他…他和Lucy
Well, he... he and Lucy...
Lucy？
Lucy?
她怎么能？
How could she?
- Mina - 不  不要  不要
- Mina. - No, don't. Don't.
你能走吗？  我想一个人呆会儿
Can you please go? I-I need to be alone right now.
Lucy在吗
Hello, Lucy.
如果你坚持要表现的像个怪物
If you insist on behaving like a monster,
我会如你所愿的
then I'm going to make you one.